odex.co 2016-12-07

# Online Document eXchange

The privacy practices of this statement ("Privacy Policy") apply to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of www.odex.co ("Website"). Through the Website, ODeX intends to provide a platform and host of services, including but not limited to (1) data entry and documents upload for invoice details and shipment enquires (2) online document management including issue and transfer of documents pertaining to shipment enquiries and transactions and (3) facilitation of electronic payments between you and beneficiary thereof (4) data collection and Payment Management to enable addition of e-convenience fees (5) seamless payment and information management and (6) such other ancillary services to facilitate the above ("Services"). In this Privacy Policy, references to "you" or "User" shall mean references to the End User of the Website, all its contents and the Services (defined below) offered through the Website. The terms "we", "us" and "our" shall mean ODeX. 

Your privacy is very important to us. We at www.odex.co ("ODeX") do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website. 

This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services; we collect from you and what may happen to that information. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is referred to and subject to the Terms of Use, User E-consent and the User Licence Agreement.

##  Information Collected under the Website 

The types of personal information ODeX may collect through the Website shall include but not limit to: 
  * 1\. Contact information, Individual and/or business (such as name, company name, job position, postal address, telephone numbers and email address) 
  * 2\. Contact information of others to whom users ask us to send information, as permitted by law 
  * 3\. Cookie data and other browser-related information as further described in the “Information We Collect By Automated Means” section of this Online Privacy Notice, and 
  * 4\. Other information that may be provided through the Sites (including through comments or questions fields)

## IP addresses and cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us to: 
  * 1\. estimate our usage size and usage pattern;
  * 2\. store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests;
  * 3\. speed up your searches; and
  * 4\. recognise you when you return to our site. 
Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. 

When you use our Website, we collect and store your personal information from you. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. To fully use our Website, you will need to register using our online registration form, where you may be required to provide us with your contact and identity information, residence / place of business information, billing information, bank account details and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Website. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You may provide us with a User ID. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our Website. We use this information to protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

## Where we store your personal data

  * The data that we collect from you will not be transferred to or stored at a destination outside India. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 
  * Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
  * Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, We cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once We have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Use of the Information Collected under the Website

  * __Establish and manage your ODeX account or reset your password.
  * __Initiate Data and documents transfer pertaining to the Services and obtain logistics information and other information thereunder.
  * __Respond to your inquiry or communicate with you about your requests, questions and comments.
  * __Send information under the Services to you and/or your contacts as the case may be.
  * __Operate, evaluate and improve our Services.
  * __Protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, claims and other liabilities.
  * __Ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * __Provide you with information or services that you request from us or which We feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * __Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and the provisions of this Privacy Policy.
  * __Allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  * __Notify you about changes to our service.

At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy. If you provide us with your financial information, we use your information to provide associated support. You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, customize the Website's content, layout and services, and to improve the Website's content and offer additional services. These uses improve the Website and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Website. You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, administrative notices, additional services offered, and communications relevant to your use of the Website. By accepting the Terms of Use (add hyperlink) and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications in your profile. You may make changes to your profile at any time.

## Your Rights and Choices

As stated hereinabove, We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information we collect about you, except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may share personal information with service providers who perform services on our behalf based on our instructions. We do not authorize these service providers to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. Examples of these service providers include entities that verify information and provide web hosting, analytics and marketing services. We also may share the personal information we obtain with our subsidiaries and affiliates. 

In addition, we may disclose information about you 

  * __if we are required to do so by applicable law or legal process,
  * __to law enforcement authorities or other government entities, and
  * __when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity. We also reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).
By using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website by ODeX. 

## Your Rights and Choices

We offer you certain choices in connection with the personal information we collect from you. You may choose not to receive email communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails. To update your preferences or submit a request, please contact us as indicated in the “How To Contact Us” section of this Privacy Policy. To the extent provided by the law of your jurisdiction, you may request access to the personal information we maintain about you or request that we correct, amend, delete or block the information by contacting us as indicated below. Where provided by law, you may withdraw any consent you previously provided to us or object at any time on legitimate grounds to the processing of your personal information, and we will apply your preferences going forward. 

## Data Transfers 

We may transfer the personal information we collect about you through the Sites to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## How We Protect Personal Information

We maintain administrative, organizational, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information obtained through the Sites against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use. 

## Links To Other Websites and Apps

Our Sites may provide links to other websites or apps for your convenience and information. These websites may operate independently from us. Linked sites and apps may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we strongly suggest you review. To the extent any linked websites are not owned or controlled by us, we are not responsible for the websites’ or apps’ content, any use of the websites or apps, or the privacy practices of the websites or apps. 

## Security

When provide or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by support@odex.co. You also may write to: Address: Odex India Solutions Pvt. Ltd., 606-607, Damji Shamji Corporate Square, Laxmi Nagar, Ghatkopar East, Mumbai – 400 075. India.
